<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<changeinfo>
<changes app_ver="05.13">
    <![CDATA[
- Now you can select the SetPack for each bubble. Press R on the selected game.<br>
- Fixed error with the STITLE when creating bubbles (max length 52).<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.12">
    <![CDATA[
- Added PSP/PSX image set for bubble creation.<br>
- Added option description at submenu.<br>
- Added Adrenaline customized option enable/disable to ABM submenu.<br>
- Added a new bubble color similar to original PSP/PSX bubbles.<br>
- Added chinese support (download font from github repo and place at ux0:data/ABM/font)<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.11">
    <![CDATA[
- Compatible with Adrenaline v6.7 and Adrenaline Bubble Booter v.08<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.10">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed reboot error (reboot loop). :( <br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.09">
    <![CDATA[
- Fix support for iso/cso/pbp in xmc0.<br>
- Sort by Device (ux0,ur0,uma0, imc0, xmc0).<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.08">
    <![CDATA[
- Compatible with Adrenaline v6.6 and Adrenaline Bubble Booter v.07<br>
- Added support for iso/cso/pbp in xmc0 (Use Vitashell for mount xmc0).<br>
- Fix "startup.png" images<br>
- Support added for frameX.png images (with X from 1 to 5).<br>
- Sort by ID.<br>
- Light aesthetic changes and clean up code.<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.07">
    <![CDATA[
- Fix error C2-12828-1 on ABM bubbles.<br>
- Added Auto Repair boot.bin option on the START button submenu (changes the customized option to YES on the old Bubbles from ABM 5.04).<br>
- Now the bg0.png is shown at Bubbles Edit screen.<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.06">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed reboot error (reboot loop). :( <br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.05">
    <![CDATA[
	- Compatible with Adrenaline v6.4 and Adrenaline Bubble Booter v.06<br>
	- Auto-Conversion of boot.inf files to boot.bin files needed for ABB v.06<br>
	- In the Edit Bubble Screen this are the available combinations:<br>
	- Driver (INFERNO/MARCH33/NP9660).<br>
	- Execute (EBOOT.BIN/EBOOT.OLD/BOOT.BIN).<br>
	- Customized: (YES/NO).<br>
	- Now when showing the bubble's linked game path will be highlighted green if the content is found, if not found will be highlighted orange.<br>
	- *NOTE: If the game linked to your bubble is not there anymore the bubble will open Adrenaline or throw an error.<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.04">
    <![CDATA[
- Now you can disable the 8bit image conversion when creating or editing ABM bubbles.<br>
- *NOTE: You must be sure the images you are using are in compatible format, otherwise the bubble will fail. Enter the submenu to change this settings with start.<br>
- Some changes in the list of Inject Imgs.<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.03">
    <![CDATA[
- New option to set default pic0 and bg0 images and your own xml file for your bubbles (up to 5 sets provided by you: ux0:ABM/Set1 to ux0:ABM/Set5).<br>
- New option to sort: Category.<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.02">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed data.inf error.<br>
- Added config.bin on each bubble (adrenaline boot screen disabled).<br>
- New graphics by Wz-Jk.<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.01">
    <![CDATA[
- Compatible with Adrenaline v6.3 thanks to Lman.<br>
- Added ux0:data/ABM/crc.ini to detect the CRC32 of the skprx modules.<br>
- Added npdrmfree enable/disable option to ABM bubble edit screen.<br>
    ]]>
  <changes app_ver="05.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Added submenu for Extra Setting.<br>
- Added hability to inject images to ABM bubbles.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.11">
    <![CDATA[
- Added drop down submenu when pressing START.<br>
- Added option to choose a favorite color (Will be saved).<br>
- Added option to show the sorted list according to preferences.<br>
- Double tap when submenu is open for help.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.10">
    <![CDATA[
- Buttons X and O reassigned only when using ABM (only if required).<br>
- Fix list sorting, now ABM shows last preset option everytime.<br>
- Fix snowfall animation.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.09">
    <![CDATA[
- Support for 3.65 CFW (Thanks to Lecheerman).<br>
- Fix automatic network update (Add TLS v1.2 Support).<br>
- Updated to the latest version of ONElua.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.08">
    <![CDATA[
- Fix error when opening the OSK more than 10 times, thanks to The_Flow!.<br>
- Update eboot.bin to ONELuavita V4R0.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.07">
    <![CDATA[
- Now the iso/cso/pbp list shows the installed content, if the game is installed as a bubble already the title will be highlighted green.<br>
- Now you can choose between list sorting by Installed, Title or Modification Date.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.06">
    <![CDATA[
- Now the icons in iso/cso/pbp list are loaded "on the fly".<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.05">
    <![CDATA[
- Now you can Sort your iso/cso/pbp by Title or by Date of Modification pressing SELECT.<br>
- Pressing START in the iso/cso/pbp list will display the basic controls.<br>
- Now the Bubble icons in the "EDIT DATA/BOOT.INF" section are loaded "on the fly".<br>
- Please update your translations...New lines were added.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.04">
    <![CDATA[
- Added japanese letters support for game titles with Sony's OSK.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.03">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed error with Homebrews with odd icons, forcing the img to 8bits.<br>
- Fixed empty iso/cso/pbp list error (Press R) again!!!.<br>
- Autodetect System language and loads translation if found.<br>
- Translations moved to resources/lang and renamed to .txt<br>
- Use english_us.txt as default translation.<br>
- Automatic creation of translation sample on ux0:data/ABM/lang/english_us.txt.<br>
- Loading translation from ux0:data/ABM/lang/%language%.txt (if exists).<br>
- Loading custom ttf font from ux0:data/ABM/resources/%language%.ttf (if exists)
- Some missed strings added to langpack (updater, custom message etc.).<br>
- Some lua scripts and translation optimization.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.02">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed empty iso/cso/pbp list error.<br>
- Now you can select to resize the games icons to show in Full Bubble or keep the original psp looks (no stretched icons).<br>
- Press L or R to switch between full or no stretched icons for your bubbles.<br>
- The script lang.lua got modified, so please update your translation.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.01">
    <![CDATA[
- Support to load your own font.ttf (Must be placed in ux0:data/ABM/font.ttf).<br>
- Now you can translate ABM, you have to translate only the texts in quotation marks of the "system/lang.lua" script found in ABM<br>
- and place the translation in ux0:data/ABM/lang.lua).<br>
- Now change the background color of each bubble is individual (Press left/right to change the color).<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="04.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed error which didn't allow to install more than 30 bubbles.<br>
- Now when multi-installing more than 9 bubbles a custom keyboard will open after 10th bubble.<br>
- Now the PS button will be blocked when Getting Resources and Instaling Bubble.<br>
- Now you can select the bubble background color!!! (17 available colors).<br>
- Removed more popup messages...again!!!.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.10">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed error caused with iso/cso/pbp which didn't have icons... again!!!.<br>
- Light aesthetic changes for icons when shown in the lists.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.09">
    <![CDATA[
- Added support for iso/cso/pbp in imc0 (Use Vitashell for mount imc0).<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.08">
    <![CDATA[
- New option to single or multi uninstall  PSPEMU bubbles.<br>
- Now the bubble's icons are not stretched and look a lot better.<br>
- Now you can do multi-bubble installation.<br>
- Ps Button can be pushed to exit ABM.<br>
- Cleaned up the code a bit and more popup messages were removed.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.07">
    <![CDATA[
- Fixed crash while trying to load some functions.<br>
- Removed some popup messages.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.06">
    <![CDATA[
- Now the resources (images) for the new bubble are converted to 8bits, so dont worry aboud db rebuild.<br>
- Support for Old ABM version has been removed.<br>
- Removed restart after creating bubbles.<br>
- NOTE: If the iso/cso/hb to launch lacks of icon0.png or pic1.png then ABM will use included Lmans images.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.05">
    <![CDATA[
- Compatible with Adrenaline v6 and Adrenaline Bubble Booter VPK Edition.<br>
- On this version ABM searches for the installed Adrenaline version and adapts to work with found Adrenaline version (either v6 or v5 and lower).<br>
- Now the cloned PSP bubbles will not show up on ABM's Available PSP content list.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.01">
    <![CDATA[
- If adrenaline folder is found at ur0: then ABM will add corresponding lines to ur0:tai/config.txt, otherwise the lines will be added to ux0:tai/config.txt i adrenaline folder is found at ux0:.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  
  <changes app_ver="03.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Adrbblbooter plugin files updated to newest version (v0.5) Thks LMAN leecherman.<br>
- Added support for iso/cso/pbp in uma0 (Use Adrenaline with support for uma0).<br>
- Now options for PLUGINS and STARTDAT.PNG is Enable for default.<br>
- Added option to Enable/Disable plugins when linking content to a bubble.<br>
- Added option Edit GAMEID.txt within ABM for Custom Bubbles (no need to restart):<br>
- Ln1: Path to the iso/cso/pbp file.<br>
- Ln2: UMD driver (INFERNO\MARCH33).<br>
- Ln3: Execute Boot (EBOOT.BIN\EBOOT.OLD\BOOT.BIN).<br>
- Ln4: Plugins state (ENABLE\DISABLE).<br>
- Ln5: STARTDAT.PNG state (ENABLE\DISABLE).<br>
- Removed adrbblbooter_nostartdat.suprx.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  
  <changes app_ver="02.10">
    <![CDATA[
- Now you can press [] to install M33 driver from start screen (for iso/cso files only).<br>
- NEW OPTION ICON0.DDS: Added the option to use pic1.png to show as bg0.png, and to set icon.dds to be shown in full bubble (but, to use this feature, te game must have been booted once and changes will revert after a db rebuild).<br>
- More Code got cleaned up a bit.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>

  <changes app_ver="02.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Adrbblbooter plugin files updated to newest version (v0.4) Thks LMAN leecherman.<br>
- Added the option to use selected content's pic1 as STARTDAT.PNG if found, otherwise Lman's plugin default STARTDAT.PNG will be used.<br>
- Now the function Disable Adrbblbooter Bubbles allows to:<br>
- Eliminate the GAMEID.TXT and corresponding STARTDAT.png files from path "ux0:adrbblbooter/bubblesdb/".<br>
- Eliminate corresponding lines from ux0:tai/config.txt and reload config.<br>
- Eliminate the PBOOT.PBP from chosen bubble.<br>
- Code got cleaned up a bit.<br>
- Some stetic changes.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
 
  <changes app_ver="01.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Initial release 'POC'.<br>
- Adrbblbooter plugin files. Thks LMAN leecherman.<br>
- Added automatic network update. app will now notify you when there's a new update.<br>
- Support get and view complete list of content of PSPemu.<br>
- Added option Enable/Disable PIC1.PNG.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
</changeinfo>
