<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<changeinfo>
  <changes app_ver="03.05">
    <![CDATA[
- Compatible with Adrenaline v6 and Adrenaline Bubble Booter VPK Edition.<br>
- Now the cloned PSP bubbles will not show up on ABM's Available PSP content list.
    ]]>
  </changes>
  <changes app_ver="03.01">
    <![CDATA[
- If adrenaline folder is found at ur0: then ABM will add corresponding lines to ur0:tai/config.txt, otherwise the lines will be added to ux0:tai/config.txt i adrenaline folder is found at ux0:.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  
  <changes app_ver="03.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Adrbblbooter plugin files updated to newest version (v0.5) Thks LMAN leecherman.<br>
- Added support for iso/cso/pbp in uma0 (Use Adrenaline with support for uma0).<br>
- Now options for PLUGINS and STARTDAT.PNG is Enable for default.<br>
- Added option to Enable/Disable plugins when linking content to a bubble.<br>
- Added option Edit GAMEID.txt within ABM for Custom Bubbles (no need to restart):<br>
- Ln1: Path to the iso/cso/pbp file.<br>
- Ln2: UMD driver (INFERNO\MARCH33).<br>
- Ln3: Execute Boot (EBOOT.BIN\EBOOT.OLD\BOOT.BIN).<br>
- Ln4: Plugins state (ENABLE\DISABLE).<br>
- Ln5: STARTDAT.PNG state (ENABLE\DISABLE).<br>
- Removed adrbblbooter_nostartdat.suprx.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
  
  <changes app_ver="02.10">
    <![CDATA[
- Now you can press [] to install M33 driver from start screen (for iso/cso files only).<br>
- NEW OPTION ICON0.DDS: Added the option to use pic1.png to show as bg0.png, and to set icon.dds to be shown in full bubble (but, to use this feature, te game must have been booted once and changes will revert after a db rebuild).<br>
- More Code got cleaned up a bit.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>

  <changes app_ver="02.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Adrbblbooter plugin files updated to newest version (v0.4) Thks LMAN leecherman.<br>
- Added the option to use selected content's pic1 as STARTDAT.PNG if found, otherwise Lman's plugin default STARTDAT.PNG will be used.<br>
- Now the function Disable Adrbblbooter Bubbles allows to:<br>
- Eliminate the GAMEID.TXT and corresponding STARTDAT.png files from path "ux0:adrbblbooter/bubblesdb/".<br>
- Eliminate corresponding lines from ux0:tai/config.txt and reload config.<br>
- Eliminate the PBOOT.PBP from chosen bubble.<br>
- Code got cleaned up a bit.<br>
- Some stetic changes.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
 
  <changes app_ver="01.00">
    <![CDATA[
- Initial release 'POC'.<br>
- Adrbblbooter plugin files. Thks LMAN leecherman.<br>
- Added automatic network update. app will now notify you when there's a new update.<br>
- Support get and view complete list of content of PSPemu.<br>
- Added option Enable/Disable PIC1.PNG.<br>
    ]]>
  </changes>
</changeinfo>
